Have you ever had a summer job?
你有过暑期工经历吗？
For many young people, summer is a heady period where education stops and fun begins.
对很多年轻人来说，夏天是一段令人兴奋的时光——学业告一段落，欢乐正式开启。
That said, holidays, festivals and time spent with friends cost money.
但话虽如此，度假、过节以及和朋友相聚都需要花钱。
And the very group who have the time to capitalise on the fun summer has to offer may not have the funds to do so.
而恰恰是那些有时间享受夏天乐趣的年轻人，可能没有足够的资金去实现。
The solution?
解决方案是什么？
A summer job.
一份暑期工。
The concept of cash-strapped students and younger members of society being gainfully employed over the summer period is not a new one.
手头拮据的学生和年轻群体在暑期从事有报酬的工作，这并不是什么新鲜事。
And there are opportunities out there for those who want to earn.
对于那些想赚钱的人来说，机会确实存在。
For me it was tending bar at a bowling alley.
我当年的暑期工是在保龄球馆当调酒师。
Vacancies can range from roles as mundane as fry cook, to seasonal work at a theme park, or a cushy job with comfortable conditions.
暑期职位五花八门，既有煎锅厨师这样平淡无奇的工作，也有主题公园的季节性岗位，或是条件舒适的轻松工作。
In many cases, the jobs only pay minimum wage, which may only tide you over.
很多情况下，这些工作只支付最低工资，可能仅够勉强维持生计。
But the money is not the only thing that's gained.
但赚到的钱只是其中的一部分而已。
"Summer and Saturday jobs prepare young people for successful careers in later life, teaching vital 'soft skills'," says UK Work and Pensions secretary Ester McVey in the Daily Mail.
英国就业与养老金大臣埃丝特·麦克维在《每日邮报》中表示：“暑期工和周六兼职能为年轻人未来的职业生涯打下良好基础，教会他们至关重要的‘软技能’。”
Indeed, when talking about their experiences of summer jobs, people asked for a BBC News article said they got "invaluable training" and learnt skills such as punctuality, tolerance, and the importance of hard graft.
事实上，在接受英国广播公司新闻采访时，人们谈到暑期工经历时表示，他们获得了“宝贵的培训”，并学会了守时、包容以及努力工作的重要性。
These opportunities are thought to be so important that the UK government has placed 20,000 summer job vacancies on a dedicated portal on its Find a Job website.
这些机会被认为非常重要，因此英国政府在其“找工作”网站的专门入口上发布了2万个暑期职位空缺。
This move comes at a time of apparent need.
这一举措出台之际，社会显然存在相关需求。
The percentage of young people working while studying has more than halved since 1997, falling from 42% to 18% in 2014.
自1997年以来，边上学边工作的年轻人比例已经减少大半，从42%降至2014年的18%。
Those are the findings of a UK government report on the death of the Saturday job.
这是英国政府一份关于“周六兼职消亡”的报告得出的结论。
Ester McVey believes this is because young people are choosing to focus more on education rather than earning extra money.
埃丝特·麦克维认为，这是因为年轻人选择更专注于学业，而不是赚取外快。
But that isn't the only problem.
但这并非唯一的问题。
It isn't always easy to get a job, as 20-year-old Liberty O'Hagan, a student from Worthing, found.
找一份暑期工并不总是那么容易，来自沃辛的20岁学生利伯蒂·奥哈根就有这样的体会。
She told the BBC employers see summer workers as a waste of training resources since they inevitably return to university.
她告诉英国广播公司，雇主们认为暑期工是对培训资源的浪费，因为他们最终都会回到大学。
Not to mention, by working all summer, you may feel you have missed out on the experiences and opportunities your friends have had – travelling and having fun.
更不用说，整个夏天都在工作，你可能会觉得自己错过了朋友所拥有的经历和机会——比如旅行和玩乐。
While a summer job may not be a dream job, it can teach you things for "a successful future," says Ester McVey in a piece for the Telegraph.
埃丝特·麦克维在为《每日电讯报》撰写的一篇文章中表示，虽然暑期工可能不是理想的工作，但它能教授你“未来成功”的宝贵经验。
What students may consider a means to an end, can, in fact, become a worthwhile career-making endeavour.
学生们可能认为暑期工只是赚钱的手段，但事实上，它可能成为一项有价值的、助力职业生涯的活动。